Organ Trail is a horror, western, drama film directed by Michael Patrick Jann.
A young Abigale Archer is left friendless and alone in a brutal Montana winter during the 1870s—fighting for survival
and to retrieve her one earthly possession, her family’s horse, from a gang of bloodthirsty bandits.
Abby, played by Zoé De Grand Maison.
Pa, played by Mather Zickel.
Ma, played by Lisa LoCicero.
Cassidy, played by Olivia Grace Applegate.
Rhys, played by Nicholas Logan.
Logan, played by Sam Trammell.
Organ Trail is a 2023 American horror Western film directed by Michael Patrick Jann, written by
Megan Turner, and starring Zoé De Grand Maison, Mather Zickel, and Lisa LoCicero.
Set in the 1870s on the Oregon Trail, the story follows Abigale Archer as she attempts to retrieve her
family's horse while fighting against the outlaws that killed her parents and brother.
The film explores themes of winter, montana, 1870s.
The tone is dark and emotional.